<Document>
  # Welcome to the Colossus Sector.

  You wake up... Somewhere. Maybe you're a marine from the local Federation flagship, maybe you're a vanguard who obeys only the Sultan, maybe you're just some lonely schmuck who's down on their luck throwing the dice in one last gambit.
  Regardless how you've gotten here, things are very different from "conventional" Space Station 14 lore.

  - [bold]Nanotrasen is destroyed.
  - [bold]The Syndicate is shattered.
  - [bold]It has been decades since the Corporate War that started this all.[/bold]

  Throw away preconceptions of being yet another generic corporate wage-slave in a retro-modern cold war. In the Colossus sector, you only truly owe loyalty to yourself. Watch your back.

  The following sections contain important context to the story of the world you find yourself in. [color=red][bold]It is highly recommended you at least read the content in this primer.[/bold][/red]

  # The Monolith

  You, and everyone else here, are within the influence of a mythical anomalous region commonly referred to as "The Monolith".
  This region encompasses what is known in common starmaps as [color=orange]the Colossus sector[/color], on the fringe of civilized space in the Perseus arm.
  "The Monolith" causes many strange phenomena, including (but not limited to) sentient fleshbeasts, highly advanced automated killing machines, mysterious forms of matter, and Blue Lobsters, almost all of which will cause a quick demise to the unprepared explorer.
  It also creates significant interference at the fringes of space - Those who enter the Colossus sector often are unable to leave.

  Not much is known about the Monolith zone, but since its discovery it has caused significant scientific intrigue attracting many different people like a second Great Expansion.

  # Factions

  It has been a long time since the Corporate War that ripped the galaxy in two. The ashes of this conflict include:

  - The [color=cyan]Trans-Solarian Federation (TSF)[/color], the surviving half of the Confederacy which took advantage of remnant corporate technology in the wake of armed conflict. It uses defensive tactics and advanced technology, but is stretched for resources.

  - The [color=orange]Phaethon Dynasty Vanguard (PDV)[/color], an old imperial house native to the Colossus sector that got boosted into galactic relevance with the discovery of the Monolith radius. They are aggressive and use effective tactics, but struggle for technological advancement.

  The TSF and the PDV are currently in armed conflict. The TSF demand the Syndicate technology now integrated into most PDV equipment *and* the property the Dynasty now inhabit, while the Dynasty is defending their self-proclaimed holy land with questionable tactics.
  Due to the anomalous interference at the fringes of the Colossus sector, the local Federation military is seperated from their main battalions, and the Dynasty is still a developing power. This has lead to a localized stalemate.
  No side is morally correct - Syndicate-originating technology is often unethical, and the TSF may be overstepping their bounds, but what is certain is that this conflict brings yet another danger to the already deadly sector.

</Document>
