<Document>
  # Reptilians

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobReptilian" Caption=""/>
  </Box>


  ## Food
  Reptilians are capable of eating raw meat, but will get ill from consuming chocolate or any other food containing theobromine.


  ## Physical properties
  They can drag objects with their tail, keeping both their hands free.

  They receive [color=#FFA500]15%[/color] less damage from slash and [color=#FF0000]5%[/color] less damage from heat, but [color=#FFA500]25%[/color] more damage from blunt.

  Their raw melee is way more powerful than human - 8 slash with 1.5 attack rate


  ## Claws
  Reptilians are equipped with dangerous claws that have different stages.

  - Stage 0 - [color=#FFA500]8 slash damage.[/color]
  - Stage 1 - [color=#FFA500]11 slash damage.[/color] [color=#FFDEAD]Gun spread is increased by 10%, Handheld weapon damage is decreased by 5%[/color]
  - Stage 2 - [color=#FFA500]13 slash damage, 2 piercing damage.[/color] [color=#FFDEAD]Gun spread is increased by 25%, Handheld weapon damage is decreased by 13%.[/color] Starting from this stage, you are capable of wideswinging with your claws
  - Stage 3 - [color=#FFA500]15 slash damage, 5 piercing damage.[/color] [color=#FFDEAD]Gun spread is increased by 45%, Handheld weapon damage is decreased by 25%[/color]
  - Stage 4 - [color=#FFA500]18 slash damage, 12 piercing damage.[/color] [color=#FFDEAD]You are not capable of using all guns but bows anymore, Handheld weapon damage is decreased by 50%.[/color]

  ### Cutting Claws

  Using [color=#FFA500]wirecutters[/color], you can cut Reptilian's claws, reducing their stage by 1 and resetting the current growth progress.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Wirecutter" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  ### Chemicals

  Certain chemicals allow greater control over Reptilian claw growth. Phenoxzine boosts claw growth by 20x, while Meroxzine pauses all claw growth entirely. Both metabolize slowly, allowing long term usage to be effective.

  <GuideReagentEmbed Reagent="Phenoxzine"/>
  <GuideReagentEmbed Reagent="Meroxzine"/>

  ## Temperature

  Due to being cold-blooded, they are not capable of generating enough heat to sustain themselfs in the [color=#4169E1]20C[/color] environment.
  Temperatures lower than [color=#4169E1]22C[/color] are extremely dangerous for them! They will start getting [color=#FF0000]drowsy and start periodically falling unconscious[/color].
  However, they receive small regeneration and speed boost if they manage to sustain body temperature higher than [color=#FFA500]47C[/color].

  ### Heating up

  - Welders, emergency flares and campfires are now capable of heating up humanoids, including Reptilians.
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Welder" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Flare" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Bonfire" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  - Wearing winter clothes or hardsuits will let you to generate enough heat to stay somewhat comfortable.
  - Reptilians are capable of exchanging heat with other creatures by hugging them. Hugging colder creature, however, will make situation worse.
</Document>
