<Document>
  # DOCKYARD 'MOTLEY ANNE'
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ConveyorBelt"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AFInterceptor"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockShuttleSyndicateRogueLocked"/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 1-3

	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] AME

	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None

	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] Included

    [color=#a4885c]Voucher:[/color] Required


  "The Motley Anne is a mobile dockyard manufactured on demand by the House Ikarus's Economic Divisions military production line for Vanguard use. It provides a closer back line for engagements in order to safely and quickly resupply.

IED's expert logistics sector has determined that in order to produce the Motley efficiently, rather than expending military salaries, resource quotas must be met to make up for the dip in labor and supply costs."

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the dual AME setup is in place.
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the rear APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC units current Load* (W).
  - Check that the front APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC units' current Load* (W).

  ## 1.2. AME unit.
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeController"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeJar"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the AME unit has at least one core.
  - Make sure the injector is adjacent to the shielding.
  - Check that the AME unit is connected to the cable terminal of your SMES via HV.
  - Check the fuel remaining of the AME unit.
  - Set the AME unit output power to 2 injections.
  - Enable Injection.

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the O2 canister is anchored to the BLUE connector port.
  - Check that the N2 canister is anchored to the RED connector port.
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to the correct mixing ratio (~22% Oxygen, ~78% Nitrogen).
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to 101.325kPa.
  - Enable gas mixer.

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MiniStationAnchor"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the station anchor is not active until needed.

  ## Fighters

  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PDVMotleyAnneCarrierComputer"/>
  </Box>


  - The fighters produced by Motley Anne are controlled using an advanced integrated and semi-automated flight system. The onboard AI servers allow the ships to perform basic commands using the console within Motley Anne's bridge.
  - Some fighters require manual loading of ammunition to function properly. Read descriptions often!

  ## Sidenotes

   - The Motley Anne comes with gas miners for resupply at any time.
   - The SMES array located in the engineering section has room for additional batteries to be charged and used elsewhere.
   - The small compartment in the dockyard can be used for a silo to provide universal materials to the mech stations.
   - The dockyard is intended to hold artillery for fighters to resupply quickly and redeploy from their respective ports.
   - The server inside the dockyard compartment comes with universal ammo for producing fighter bomber artillery.
</Document>
