<Document>
# Roleplay Rule 7
## Safe Zones: Sanctuary and Conduct

[color=green][bold]Safe Zones[/bold][/color] (Colossus Central, Medical Dispatch, and a 256m radius around each) are neutral sanctuary areas for all players, regardless of group or affiliation.

[color=yellow][bold]Admin Summary:[/bold][/color]
- Safe Zones are neutral and protect everyone unless you cause trouble.
- Do not steal ID's, ships, or supplies off of ships.
- Do not attack ships unless they were in combat no more than 2 minutes prior.
- Contraband is only actionable if used or if the contraband holder is causing trouble.
- Troublemakers are handed to CO Security Guards, not factions or groups.
- Use non-lethal force when practical; lethal force is acceptable if non-lethal would put you or others at serious risk.
- If you wish to launch an attack that can harm uninvolved persons, send several warnings for a minimum of 5 minutes.
- Staff may intervene in cases of abuse or unclear situations.

[color=red]Actions within safezones that will result in administrative action:[/color]
-- Stealing ID's and/or ship vouchers
-- Stealing ships and/or supplies off of them
-- Attacking ships that were not in combat within the last 2 minutes
  
[color=yellow][bold]Actions that will lead to [color=red]removal[/color] of your safezone protection:[/bold][/color]
-- Crimes on the safezone (Trespass, Vandalism of the station)
-- Being in safezone radius while having an active [color=red]command[/color] bounty on yourself.
-- Being in safezone radius as ghost-role antagonist (Cortical borer, Asakim, Chimera, ADM/ADC).
-- Failure to comply with station head requirements (Overseer for Colossus Central, as an example).

- If you cause trouble in a Safe Zone or it's radius (see above), you [color=yellow]forfeit protection[/color] and may be detained. [color=yellow][bold]Detained individuals must be handed over to CC Judges or the Overseer for processing, not to any faction or group.[/bold][/color]

- [color=yellow][bold]Use non-lethal force for arrests and detainment when practical. If non-lethal options would put you or others at serious risk, using lethal force is acceptable.[/bold][/color]

- [color=yellow][bold]If you wish to launch an attack on a safezone which may lead to deaths or damage to those not involved, you must send several warnings to evacuate the safezone for a minimum of 5 minutes[/color][/bold]

- [color=green][bold]Contraband is allowed in Safe Zones.[/bold][/color] It is only actionable if used or if you are causing trouble. Wearing or carrying immediate gear is tolerated; stashing or distributing is not. Destroying turrets that detect contraband is allowed, but causes your safezone protection removal.

- Entering a Safe Zone does not end ongoing fights or consequences, you [bold]may continue fights[/bold] if it moves into a safezone, while attempting to [bold]minimize[/bold] damage to the safezone.

</Document>
